パキッ パキッ
ドドォーン！
ドォーン！
ドドォーーン‼
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)なんだ？ あれは｡
What is that?
That is Dromos.
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)あれは ドロモス…｡
You know of it?
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)ご存じなのですか？
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)我々 神から奪った➡
It is a weapon of mass destruction
数々の禁じられた技術により
作り上げられた破壊兵器｡
born from the forbidden knowledge
humanity stole from us.
We cannot stay here!
このままではいけません！
All forces,
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙの声)全軍に告げます｡
直ちに撤退しなさい｡
fall back at once.
なっ…｡
城の制圧は目前です！ なぜ!?
We are moments away
from taking the castle! Why?
This is a direct order.
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙの声)命令です｡ これ以上
この地で戦うことはなりません｡➡
We must not fight here any longer.
今すぐ 神界に戻るのです！
(軍神)なぜだ!?
We must return to heaven immediately!
Why?! The humans are on their last legs!
(軍神)
人間どもは もはや 虫の息だ！
Why will you not withdraw?
なぜ すぐに撤退しないのです！
私たちだけでも
先に戻りましょう｡
We should at least fall back without them.
パーン！
What are you talking about?
≪(ｴﾙ)何言ってるの？
We have not saved my mother yet.
(ｴﾙ)
まだ お母さんを助けてないよ｡
Rage of Bahamut
(ﾌｧﾊﾞﾛ･ﾚｵｰﾈ)
戦場の真っただ中に出ちまったな｡
Seems like we popped up
in the middle of a battlefield.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ひとまず
人目を避けられる所に移動しよう｡
We should move to an area
where we won't be seen.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)おい リタ｡ どこへ行く！
Hey, Rita!
Where are you going?!
何!?
(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)ああっ…｡
What?!
やばい気がする｡
I've got a bad feeling about this.
やめなさい エル！
一緒に逃げるのです！
Stop, El!
You must retreat with us!
うわっ…｡ きゃあ～！
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)あっ エル！
えっ？
El!
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)うっ！
バシュー！
うおっ！
ううっ… わあ～！
- Nina!
- Favaro!
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)ニーナ！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ファバロ～！
うわぁ～！
(ｼｬﾘｵｽ17世)あっ｡
ドカーン‼
ドォーン！
Over there!
(軍神)あそこだ！
人間の王は あそこだ！➡
The human king is there!
人間の王を殺せ～！
Kill the king of man!
If this continues, we will be annihilated.
このままでは 全滅する｡
≫キン キン キン…
(剣を交える音)
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)殺すな…｡
Don't...
殺さないでくれ～！
Don't kill them!
ブスッ！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)うわぁ～！ ぐっ ぐっ…➡
ぐおっ ぐっ… うっ｡➡
ファバロは？
分からない｡
Where's Favaro?!
I don't know.
かなりの勢いで飛んでったのは
見たけど｡
I saw him get blown pretty far away.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ジャンヌ様～！
Lady Jeanne!
Nina...
ニーナ
どこへ飛ばされたのかしら｡
Where did you get blown away to?
Rage of Bahamut
脱獄は成功したようだな｡
えっ…｡
It seems that you've successfully escaped
your prison.
Your eye...
その目…｡
片目でも お前は見える｡
I can still see you with one eye.
あ… あなた どういうつもり？
｢どう｣とは？
What are you after?!
What do you mean?
Disguising yourself when you're the king,
walking around the city, dancing with me!
王様なのに
変装して 街を徘徊したり➡
私と踊ったりして！
また踊りたいのか？
ううっ！
So you want to dance again?
≪キン！
はっ！
≫キン！
助けなきゃ！
やめておけ｡
I have to save her!
Do not bother.
これ以上は逃げられない｡
There is no escape now.
協力して｡
協力？
Help me.
Help you?
キン キン！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)くっ！ ぐわっ！ うっ｡
ギュッとして｡
Hug me.
ん？
だから ギュッとして！
Hurry up and hug me!
ドカーン！
(ﾘﾀ)ええっ!?
グオォーー！
ガリッ！
ドーン！
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)はっ！
ドゴッ！
I can actually transform into a dragon.
(回想)
((実は私 竜になれるんです))
あっ… ニーナ！
Nina!
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ジャンヌ様 こちらです！
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)うん｡
Lady Jeanne!
This way!
グオォー！
グオォー…
ボォン！
ボォーン！
すごっ！
(２人)あっ あぁ…｡
Wow!
バシャーン！
ドカーーン‼
グルル グルル…
裸のレディーに
気安く触るんじゃないわよ｡
Keep your dirty mitts off a lady
when she's naked.
何者だ？
(ﾘﾀ)通りすがりのゾンビよ｡
Who are you?
Just your average zombie passing by.
ピューッ(指笛)
待て｡
Stop.
逃がすと思うか？
Did you think I would let you get away?
Go, Rita!
≪(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)行け リタ！
(ﾘﾀ)あんたは？
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ここは私に任せろ｡
What about you?
Leave this to me!
はぁ…｡ そんなに
飛んでったアフロが気になんの？
You're really worried
about that dumb Afro, aren't you?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)違う｡ 早く行け！
No!
Just go already!
(ﾘﾀ)死ぬんじゃないわよ｡
Don't die, okay?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ふん｡
≪(兵士)やっちまえ！ おらっ！➡
Get him!
Kill him!
≪やれ！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)うわっ｡➡
ぐわっ！
(兵士たち)おらっ！
殺すなよ｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)うっ！
Do not kill him.
神は退いた｡ 今は それでいい｡
The gods have retreated.
That is good enough for now.
城へ帰るぞ｡
(隊長)はっ｡
-We are returning to the castle.
-Yes, My Lord.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)
エルは まだ気を失ったままです｡
El is still unconscious.
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)なぜ 人の王は➡
How was the king of man
able to create such a thing?
あんなものに
たどりつけたのでしょうか…｡
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)あの破壊兵器ですか？
Do you mean the weapon?
That weapon is a relic of the old world
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)
あの技術は ミスタルシアに➡
まだ
神も悪魔も 人も現れる以前の➡
from a time before man, demons,
and gods roamed Mistarcia.
旧世界の遺産です｡➡
たとえ
我々から石盤を奪ったとしても➡
Even if they had stolen
the stone slabs from us,
それを集結し 作り上げる知識を
人が持つなどありえません｡
mankind should not have been able to
gather them together and actually build it.
あの兵器は
世界のバランスを崩し➡
That weapon has the power to destroy
the balance of the world
崩壊へと導く力です｡
and lead it down the path
of its own destruction.
バハムートのように！
はっ…｡
Just as Bahamut!
It's okay, it's okay
I cast the usual spell
Stagnation, stagnation
My words and heart are at odds
Default
I've taken all the paint
And mixed up all the colors
Until you're left with me
So fragile
Yet strong
Close to overflowing
But not spilling
Because I'm incomplete
I won't amount to much
This is just a good luck charm
I'm not asking for your help
I was just clinging to you
Let's end it all today
I'm done living this pointless life
I've taken my last, pointless breath
To whom it may concern
See ya and goodbye
I killed the person I was yesterday
To whom it may concern
See ya and goodbye
A new morning is coming
ねえ 私 大丈夫だった？
Hey, was I okay?
Yes, we were all able to live
thanks to you.
(ﾘﾀ)ええ｡ ニーナのおかげで➡
み～んな助かったわ｡
へへっ｡
でも カイザルさんと師匠は
置いてっちゃったんでしょ？
But we left Mister Kaisar and
Master Favaro behind, didn't we?
それに…｡
Also...
≫ガチャ(ﾄﾞｱの開閉音)
(ﾘﾀ)そうね｡➡
That's true.
だから 私は 様子を見てくるわ｡
That's why I'm going to go take a look.
えっ！ ちょっ… 危ないよ｡
What?! It's too dangerous!
ニーナ あんたは
聖女様と一緒にいなさい｡➡
Nina, you stay with the holy maiden.
王都に戻っちゃダメよ
犯罪者で 脱獄犯なんだから｡
And don't go back to the capital.
You're criminals and now escapees.
リタは？
王都に戻るわ｡
What about you, Rita?
I'm going back to the capital,
カイザルとアフロの
具合を見にね｡➡
to check on Kaisar and the Afro.
Well...
じゃあ ニーナをお願い｡
Take care of Nina.
ああ～！ リタ～！
Wait, Rita!
はぁ～あ…｡
これから どうします？
What should we do now?
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)私は 神の国に行きたい｡
I would like to go to the land of the gods.
What?
El was there on that battlefield.
先の戦に エルはいた｡
あの光はエルだ｡
That light was El.
Mugaro?
ムガロちゃん…｡
撤退した神々は
神の国に戻ったはず｡
The gods must have withdrawn
back to their homelands.
今は それが エルにつながる
唯一の手がかりなのだが…｡
That is my only lead to find El.
私には
神の国の場所が分からない｡
But I do not know where
the land of the gods is.
Oh, I might be able to do
something about that.
あっ それ なんとかなるかも｡
えっ？➡
What? Is that true?
それは誠か？
うん｡
Yeah, the old lady back in my village
would talk about it all the time.
確か 里のばあちゃんが
昔 よく行ってたって｡
Village?
里？
竜の里｡
The Dragon Village! My hometown.
私のふるさとだよ｡
行こう ニーナの里へ｡
Then let us go to your village.
えっ いいの!?
What? Really?!
Yes, we have no other leads.
ああ｡ 他に手がかりはない｡
行け～ ヒッポグリフ～！
Go, Hippogriff!
Behold, the power of Dromos!
The power of the stone!
It synced with me and those hand beams
went boom! And boom!
More valiant than anything!
Next time on Rage of Bahamut:
Virgin Soul, "Homecoming"
Beams went boom!
BAHA SOUL!!
Baha baha baha soul.
Watch next time too, all right?